We Are Never Ever Getting Back Together
压制:随Feng
歌手:Taylor Swift
I remember when we broke up the first time
我记得我们第一次分手的时候
Saying this is it, I've had enough
我说就这样吧 我已经受够了
Cause like we hadn't seen each other in a month
因为好像我们一个月都没见面了
when you said you needed space, what?
因为你说你需要空间… 什么？
Then you come around again and say baby
然后你又回到我身边 你说
I miss you and I swear i'm gonna change, trust me
宝贝我想你 我发誓我会改 你相信我
Remember how that lasted for a day
可持续了有一天么?
I say I hate you, we break up, you call me, I love you
我说 我讨厌你。 我们又分手了 你打电话说 我爱你
Oh Woo-Oh
We called it off again last night
昨晚你又打给我
But oh woo-oh, this time I'm telling you, I'm telling you
但是 这次我会告诉你 我会告诉你
We are never ever ever getting back together
我们再也不能一起回到过去了
You go talk to your friends, talk to my friends, talk to me
你让你我的朋友都来说服我
But we are never ever ever ever getting back together
但我们真的再也不能一起回到过去了
Like, ever
真的
I'm really gonna miss you picking fights
我真的很想念那些你挑起的争执
And be falling for it, screaming that I'm right
我曾大声告诉你我是对的
And you would hide away and find your peace of mind
然后你逃避 你躲在自己的思维里
with some indie record that's much cooler than mine
和一些比我酷得多的想法中寻找自己
Oh, oh, you called me up again tonight
今晚你又一次打了我的电话
But oh woo-oh-oh, this time I'm telling you, I'm telling you
但这一次我告诉你 听清楚
We are never ever ever getting back together
我们再也不能一起回到过去了
You go talk to your friends, talk to my friends, talk to me
你让你我的朋友都来说服我
But we are never ever ever ever getting back together
但我们真的再也不能一起回到过去了
I used to think that we were forever ever
我曾经以为我们会走很远
And I used to say never say never
我曾经说过永远不要说分离
Then he calls me up and he's like
他打电话给我 然后这样说
'I still love you,' and I'm like
“我还爱你.” 然后我就说
this is exhausting, you know, we are never getting back together – like ever
我太累了...你知道的...我们再也不能一起回到过去了
We are never ever ever getting back together
我们再也不能一起回到过去了
You go talk to your friends, talk to my friends, talk to me
你让你我的朋友都来说服我
But we are never ever ever ever getting back together.
但我们再也不能一起回到过去了
Oh Woo-oh oh
压制:随Feng
You go talk to your friends, talk to my friends, talk to me
你让你我的朋友都来说服我
But we are never ever ever ever getting back together
但我们再也不能一起回到过去了